

About Me

Stack

Skills

Corneliu Zediu

Front-End Developer

Schwarenbergstraße 160 70184, Stuttgart

Phone: 0049/15224019045 Mail: <u>contact@corneliu-zediu.com</u>

Portfolio: corneliu-zediu.com
GitHub: github.com/corneliuzediu
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/corneliuzediu

I am a German-speaking Frontend Developer with experience in building web apps with JavaScript & Angular.

I started my IT journey with an Entry-Level Python Certificate at home and then decided to get professional training and build top class projects. Due to structured work, analytical thinking and problem solving, I have written projects alone or in teams, based on clean code principles. You're welcome to visit my public portfolio, which includes my work (e.g.: Join, El Pollo Loco, Pokedex, Ring of Fire).

I am looking forward to building on my experience and starting my career in IT in a junior developer position.

Main Stack: - JavaScript

TypeScript, Angular

- HTML, CSS/SCSS, Bootstrap

Side Stack: - Git, APIs (REST), Google Firebase

Building Applications with JavaScript & Angular:

I built landing pages and several web apps, as well as OOP-based Jump-and-Run-Games with the respective technologies.

• Working in a Software-Team:

During professional development, I did various group projects where I learned how to develop a software project in a team.

• High sense of responsibility:

Working diligently and being responsible is an instinctive way of living for me.

Professional Experience

March 2019 - June 2022 Bielefeld & Stuttgart, Germany

Bershka Deutschland Gmbh / Salesman & Chico Respo

Bershka is a popular fashion retailer that offers trendy and affordable clothing and accessories for young men and women.

- Attentive customer service with personalized solution
- Proficient collection, analysis and interpretation of KPIs in order to take the best data-driven decisions
- Effective guiding, training and support for the team members

November 2017 - June 2018 Bucharest, Romania

Altius Fotovoltaics Srl / Economical Engineer

Altius is a manufacturer of photovoltaic panels with HQ in Bucharest and the factory in Giurgiu, Romania

- Efficiently operating and managing a wide range of industrial machinery and equipment with precision and expertise.
- Providing comprehensive and user-friendly documentation and instructions for optimizing factory processes and maximizing operational efficiency.

All summers: 2014 - 2017 Sandusky, Ohio, USA

Cedar Point / General Area Supervisor

Cedar Point, known as the "Roller Coaster Capital of the World," is a premier amusement park in Sandusky, Ohio.

- Efficiently configuring, managing and maintaining hardware components for optimal performance and functionality
- Effective overseeing, guiding and coordination of a team

Education

July 2022 - April 2023 Munich, Germany

Developer Akademie / Qualified Web-Developer Front-End

Project based coding academy. Main Stack: JavaScript, Angular

Portfolio: www.corneliu-zediu.com

Extensive Coding School, Learning Front-End Development, Coding, Agile Project Management and building several projects in teams and alone.

February 2022 – now Stuttgart, Germany

HarvardX CS50 / Certificate in Computer Science

CS50's Introduction to Computer Science

Relative topics include algorithms, data structure, software engineering, etc. Programming languages: C, Python, SQL and Javascript, CSS and HTML.

February 2022 – May 2022 Stuttgart, Germany Python Institute OpenEDG / Certificate in Python language

PCEP- Certified Entry-Level Python Programmer

The Course covers "Computer Programming Python Fundamentals", "Conditional Block and Loops" and "Data Collection".

Languages

Romanian: native
English: fluent
German: good